I've never seen something like that, and the noise of it when it was going up was insane.
And I asked Grandpa, would you go in it?
And he goes, "What's up guys, welcome back to the channel.
Today we are on Trump Force 1."
Don't you see the Starship rocket launch at SpaceX?
Oh, we got a Nutella girl here.
Hey guys.
They actually got really good Nutella froyo the other night.
Oh, it was so good.
They opened a 16 handle.
The Nutella was...
It shows the pumpkin spice.
I love pumpkin spice.
I hate pumpkin spice.
What do you like?
I got Nutella flavored ice cream, and then I got this Nutella like spread crunch.
Got the pumps of Nutella, and I got cookie dough.
How much Nutella do you consume a week?
Consume a week?
Like of the big tops, like two?
So the edits you guys make.
Don't laugh.
The edits that I've seen on TikTok, I actually love the edits.
Especially to like the good songs, like some of the Weekend songs.
I saw one edit that was like JKR.
I think it's JKR, right baby?
Oh yeah, here.
JKR.
Yeah.
I really like that it, so keep them off amazing.
One, two, three, four, one, two, three.
One, two, three, four, one, two, three, four.
Go grab a snack of your...
Like this one, this is one panel.
Oh wait, this is clapping.
You, they meet Emma.
Do you ready?
She always cheats, so we can't play.
Oh, my God.
I won.
20 right now.
I'm sweating.
I got one question for y'all.
Who coordinated the offense?
Actually, let me break this down.
Kai asked me, what do we think we're going to wear?
I said, I just bought the Skims to off at the mall.
I think I'm gonna wear black jeans, a black belt, black shoes, and a Skims top.
She goes, where in the mall do they sell Skims?
I said, oh, Nordstrom.
I show up to her house.
She's wearing a black Skims top, a black belt, and black jeans.
Can you grab my back?
Here, this.
Do you guys hear that?
Oh, it's hard lifting, like, 200 pounds with, like, a kind of...
I think it's what, with you and your guy?
Yeah.
Wow.
Is he easier to be on?
Oh, my God.
It's making her lighter.
Oh, you can get off now.
Alright, my turn.
You can get down lower.
Get lower.
Eyes out of 45 degree, you're gonna fail.
You can do it.
Alright, first one on land wins.
New tele girl in the wild.
This is the plane.
Let me give you the tour.
You can probably sit down right there.
Thank you.
What do you think?
Pretty sick.
Very cool, right?
BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP 500.
Pretty cool stuff.
It's not everyday you get to see a plane there.
100, 50, 40,
30, 20, 10.
I
don't really know what's happening right
now.
I'm arguing with you.
I'm an MS fan girl right now.
Bryson and Neon.
Oh my god.
I'll design a rocket ship golf club for you.
I know.
With boosters in the back so you can increase your swing speed.
Just a tad.
320 coming your way?
Just for you.
Just for me, yeah.
I'm gonna need it.
Alright, alright.
Ow, ow, that hurt.
Stop.
That hurt.
Those black tiles?
Yes.
We're looking at the leeward side of the rocket.
So the other side, the windward side, has those black tiles.
Yeah, it's a little hard to see, but, so we're looking at the leeward side, the cold side, essentially.
So you can see the tiles are on the nose, but on the other side, the windward side, it's all black tiles.
And those are ceramic, basically heat shield tiles.
Basically a more advanced version of what was on the spaceship.
We're going off at 20 minutes left.
20 more minutes.
20 minutes.
Yeah.
Look, it's up at the top left.
T-minus.
What are we feeling?
I don't know.
My hair's all over the place, though.
Oh, the bread looks pretty good.
I'm really okay today.
This is
cute.
What else do you want?
I think this cookie.
That actually kind of cool.
It a star brew.
A cold brew.
The baking is very good.
Very good baking.
Oh my god.
It's very good.
Very good.
We're going to the next level.
The...
It
only comes back to
land if everything is like super green, and we had some concerns about the tower, so it was commanded to land out to sea.
Amazing.
Can they use that again?
Can they?
Get it from the city?
It's going to be probably blocked.
It's probably going to be blocked is my guess.
But it's fine.
We actually have better versions that are in production in those factories over there.
How long will it take to produce another one of those?
We already have the next one.
Well, there you go.
And it's better than that one.
There are big improvements with every success.
So what makes it better?
The specific next one we have is a lot of small improvements.
There's a big version of the fleet that will be flying next year.
That's got the version 3 of our engines.
That'll look very different.
That'll be longer and have a lot more thrust and have the next generation engines.
You can see on those screens up there, that's the ship that is now going around the Earth.
If you want to maybe get a better view if you come.
Yeah, let's go.
So it's actually going through the dock side of the Earth.
The region of Earth that it's going through is now Garth.
It'll enter the region where it's actually sunny.
It's currently sunny about 600 miles northwest of Australia, so it'll go out of Earth's shadow, and we should be able to see it land.
And that'll be pretty cool.
Watching it re-enter is pretty wild, because it's being closed like 24 hours.
It looks like special effects, because it's like every color.
It's like purple, red, white.
It's wild.
If it doesn't blow up, we do have ships to try to bring it back, to bring it back, and then we can expect it to learn more.
But this, but this one won't be reused.
This one will not be reused.
So this one is all about just learning.
It's about learning more.
This time we're going to enter at a steeper angle than before, so it's going to be a higher heating.
We'll see if some of the changes we've made to the heat shield are better.
So the last launch, you can actually see where it was getting really hot, because we've used some heat shields, so it was kind of
glowing, and little bits were melting off, and that kind of thing.
So hopefully this time the heat shield should be more robust.
We also reduced the amount of heat shielding, so there's about six feet less heat shielding on the sides.
Because we don't think that's necessary.
Jan, let's check it out.
It's kind of like, okay, it didn't explode.
Well, I guess it's, you know, sick.
Look on the bright side.
I've never seen something like that.
And the noise of it, like when it was going up, it was insane.
And I asked Grandpa, would you go in it?
And he goes, no.
He would not volunteer going in the spaceship, but it's okay.
Oh, would you?
Go in it?
Without a doubt, in a heartbeat, I'm on it.
That was crazy, that was good.
What's the g-forces going up if you were to go to man?
Is it too much for a person to handle?
No, it's fine.
Like 5 g's.
The boost backbone is doing 20 g's, so you wouldn't want to be on that.
You wouldn't want to do the flip.
What did you say the top speed was?
Well, this planet will do about 17,000 miles an hour, but going to Mars, you'd go much faster than that.
So maybe 35,000, depends on how fast you want to go to Mars, but maybe 35,000 miles an hour.
What's the quickest time frame to get to Mars with our current technology?
If you want to maximize payload, it takes six months.
You can potentially get it down to three or four months if you're willing to sacrifice payload.
Does the weight matter once you're in space as much or not really?
You've got to accelerate mass to velocity, to basically the Mars transfer velocity.
So there's a cost benefit of getting it going.
Yeah, so if you have less payload, you can go faster.
At the beginning, we'd maximize payload to be like six months.
Six months.
Like long term, you can definitely get it below three months.
So yeah.
Cool.
Fantastic.
Let's go see it.
Let's do it.
It's amazing.
Cool.
It's pretty exciting.
I mean, it's one of the most epic games that he has ever done.
Oh, for sure.
For sure.
What's harder, this or greater rifts?
Diablo.
This is much harder.
Did you ever play Fortnite?
No.
But I did play.
Quake and a bunch of other first person shooters.
What about League?
Did you play League?
If I start playing League, it will damage the space program.
Yeah, that's cool.
It's awesome.
It's an honor to have a president here.
I swear I got chills, and I never get chills besides winning tournaments.
When I win tournaments, I get the chills throughout my whole body.
This legitimately gave me chills down the back of my spine.
This was honestly one of the coolest things ever.
I think that changed my entire perspective on the world.